<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BoboLink</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">MapsActivity</string>
    <string name="open_nav">Open Navigation Drawer</string>
    <string name="close_nav">Close Navigation Drawer</string>
    <string-array name="birdwatching_tips">
        <item>Tip 1: Use quiet movements to avoid startling birds.</item>
        <item>Tip 2: Early morning is often the best time for birdwatching.</item>
        <item>Tip 3: Wear neutral-colored clothing to blend in with the environment.</item>
        <item>Tip 4: Learn to recognize bird calls and songs to identify species without visual contact.</item>
        <item>Tip 5: Invest in a good pair of binoculars for a closer look at birds.</item>
        <item>Tip 6: Carry a field guide to help identify different bird species.</item>
        <item>Tip 7: Be patient; birds may take time to reappear in a spot where they were frightened away.</item>
        <item>Tip 8: Move slowly and steadily to prevent scaring birds.</item>
        <item>Tip 9: Avoid wearing perfumes or scented lotions that may alert birds to your presence.</item>
        <item>Tip 10: Check local birding reports for recent sightings and tips.</item>
        <item>Tip 11: Visit a variety of habitats to see a wider range of species.</item>
        <item>Tip 12: Keep a safe distance from nests and young birds to avoid distressing them.</item>
        <item>Tip 13: Use a camera with a zoom lens to capture images without getting too close.</item>
        <item>Tip 14: Keep a birdwatching journal to record your observations and experiences.</item>
        <item>Tip 15: Join a local birdwatching club to learn from experienced birders.</item>
        <item>Tip 16: Use a spotting scope for observing birds at a distance in open areas.</item>
        <item>Tip 17: Be mindful of the weather, as it can affect bird behavior and visibility.</item>
        <item>Tip 18: Respect wildlife and habitat conservation laws and guidelines.</item>
        <item>Tip 19: Stay on designated trails to minimize habitat disturbance.</item>
        <item>Tip 20: Avoid using flash photography, which can startle birds.</item>
        <item>Tip 21: If birdwatching near water, remain still to observe waterfowl without alarming them.</item>
        <item>Tip 22: Learn about migratory patterns to find the best times for watching different species.</item>
        <item>Tip 23: Use bird feeders and baths to attract birds to your yard for observation.</item>
        <item>Tip 24: Minimize talking and noise to prevent scaring birds away.</item>
        <item>Tip 25: Share your bird sightings with online birding communities for citizen science contributions.</item>
        <item>Tip 26: Use apps or online resources to compare your observations with others.</item>
        <item>Tip 27: Be aware of your surroundings to avoid disturbing wildlife or putting yourself in danger.</item>
        <item>Tip 28: Practice ethical bird photography, keeping the welfare of the bird as a priority.</item>
        <item>Tip 29: Study bird behavior to understand feeding, mating, and migration habits.</item>
        <item>Tip 30: Teach children and newcomers birdwatching ethics and the importance of conservation.</item>
        <item>Tip 31: Visit bird sanctuaries and national parks dedicated to avian habitats.</item>
        <item>Tip 32: Participate in bird counts and other citizen science events.</item>
        <item>Tip 33: Be patient and enjoy the process, even if you do not spot your target species.</item>
        <item>Tip 34: Remember that the best birdwatching tool is your own senses; stay alert.</item>
        <item>Tip 35: Keep your distance from other birdwatchers to avoid creating a crowd.</item>
        <item>Tip 36: Refrain from playing recordings to attract birds, as this can disrupt their natural behaviors.</item>
        <item>Tip 37: If birdwatching in a group, coordinate with others to cover more ground.</item>
        <item>Tip 38: Regularly clean your binoculars and camera lenses for the best viewing experience.</item>
        <item>Tip 39: Practice identifying birds by silhouette, which can be handy in low-light conditions.</item>
        <item>Tip 40: Always leave the environment as you found it, taking nothing but pictures and leaving nothing but footprints.</item>
        <item>Tip 41: Study the shapes and flight patterns of birds to aid in identification.</item>
        <item>Tip 42: Keep your hands steady while using binoculars by resting your elbows on your chest.</item>
        <item>Tip 43: Learn to identify birds by their behavior and habitat preferences.</item>
        <item>Tip 44: Attend birdwatching festivals and events for unique birding opportunities and to learn from experts.</item>
        <item>Tip 45: Plant native species in your garden to attract local birds.</item>
        <item>Tip 46: When birdwatching in a group, use hand signals to communicate and point out bird locations silently.</item>
        <item>Tip 47: Familiarize yourself with the ethics of birdwatching, including not disturbing habitats and birds.</item>
        <item>Tip 48: Invest in a waterproof notebook or app to record sightings in all weather conditions.</item>
        <item>Tip 49: Take advantage of birdwatching trails and hides in nature reserves.</item>
        <item>Tip 50: Use a map and compass, or a GPS device, to navigate remote birding areas.</item>
        <item>Tip 51: Keep a list of birds you’ve seen, known as a "life list," to track your birdwatching journey.</item>
        <item>Tip 52: Experiment with different times of day; some birds are more active at dusk or just before night.</item>
        <item>Tip 53: Learn about endangered species in your area and how you can help protect them.</item>
        <item>Tip 54: Use social media and birding apps to connect with other birdwatchers and share experiences.</item>
        <item>Tip 55: Bring along a portable chair or blanket for extended birdwatching sessions.</item>
        <item>Tip 56: Stay hydrated and bring snacks, especially when birdwatching in remote areas or for long periods.</item>
        <item>Tip 57: Respect private property and do not trespass when birdwatching.</item>
        <item>Tip 58: If leading a birdwatching walk, ensure that all participants have a chance to see the birds before moving on.</item>
        <item>Tip 59: Enhance your birdwatching experience by learning about the ecology and conservation status of the areas you visit.</item>
        <item>Tip 60: Consider a lightweight, portable birding scope for distant or detailed viewing.</item>
    </string-array>


</resources>
